

# **GODFREY SAMUEL**

Software Engineer

♥: +2348082358376 
I godfreysam09@gmail.com

: Abuja-Nigeria

# **ABOUT ME**

Over the past three years, I have worked on projects and serviced clients which have helped me honed my skill as a software engineer and web developer. I have developed a good track record with frontend technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript as well as javaScript libraries such as Jquery and Reactis. I have also worked with JavaScript on backend using Node.js, Express.js and Handlebars and Embedded-JavaScript-templates as template engine for server-side rendering, I have also worked with databases such as NEDB for in-memory data storage and management, MongoDb and Mongoose for larger datasets at the backend, REST API, Graphql, Axios and browser inbuilt fetch API. I believe I have a lot to offer as an engineer who has been working hard at his craft; I have a quick grasp of new concepts and technology which is why I am working hard to build a successful career as a software engineer and hopefully be reckoned with as an expert in my field.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Esty Telecom**

Entry level | Software developer Abuja, Nigeria 2020-01-01 | 2020-09-01 Software developer, and Data sorting

### Founder epinsorter.com

2021-01-01

Programmer, Full stack Software engineer.

#### **WAAW** foundation

Full stack Web developer (MERN Stack) 2021

# **EDUCATION**

Degree: Bachelor of Science Engineering Physics

2012-11-10 | 2016-04-15

Obafemi Awolowo University Ile-Ife, Nigeria.

#### **JOB SKILLS**

**Software Development** 

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

**UX/UI** Designer

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

**English** 

**Local Dialects** 

# **CERTIFICATES & AWARDS**

Responsive Web Design: Certificate | 2019

JavaScript Algorithm and Data Structures: Certificate | 2020

Front End Libraries: Certificate | 2020

Google Cloud : Certificate | 2021

#### **PROJECTS & PORTFOLIO**

My Portfolio: http://godfreyo.link/